bookmax.net 2014-06-25

# Online Bookmarks Manager - Privacy Policy!

## Privacy Policy

### Privacy Statement Summary

Bookmax.net strives to protect your privacy. We know that your bookmarks are part of your private information and we will do all we can to protect its privacy. 

  * We will never share, rent, loan or give away your bookmarks or any other personal information to anyone. 
  * We will not send you any unwanted mail. 
  * We wil not allow other members to view your private data or bookmarks (except the ones you share in your public or team folders). 

### Privacy Statement

Bookmax.net (like many ohter sites) uses cookies to keep track of your session and improve your user experience. The cookies are small bits of information stored on your computer, they contain information for user identification and settings for the bookmarks menu. 

Bookmax.net´s registration form requires users to give us their email address. We use this email address to send the user information about his account after registration and to send username and password in case he forgets the password. 

Our system automatically detects the country, the user lives in, from the users ip address. We may use this information to suggest other web sites and bookmarks that you may be interested in. These links will only show as bookmark in the main bookmarks folder. 

Your stored bookmarks at bookmax.net are links to other sites. Bookmax.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. When you click on a link to visit another site, we will record that click in order to provide you with the ability to sort bookmarks by most visited and to help you determine which of your links are more used than others. 

### Security

Your bookmarks can only be accessed with your username and password. We highly recommend that you never share your password with anyone. If you share a computer with multiple people or use any publicly accessible computer (such as at a library or school computer lab) we recommend you log out before you leave the computer. 

We will never ask you for your password. If someone asks you for your password, please report the situation to [mail@bookmax.net ](mailto:mail@bookmax.net), as it is likely someone attempting to fraudulently gain access to you account. 

Should you wish to delete your account and completely remove your account information from our database, you can cancel your account by selecting "Delete Account" in the "Settings" of your Bookmax.net account. In that case your user information and bookmarks will be completely removed from our database. 

### Correct/Update your data

You can change your account information, when you login to bookmax.net [here](http://my.bookmax.net/login), then click on the "Settings" menu button in the top navigation bar and change the data on the settings page. 

### Contact

If you have any questions about the security or privacy of bookmax.net don´t hesitate to send us your question via email. 

Bookmax.net,
